(Sheldon:)Incidentally, one can get beaten up
in school...
(Sheldon:)...simply
by referring to oneself as "one."
(Sheldon:)I'm making English muffins.
Would you like an English muffin?
(Penny:)Oh, thanks, I'm not hungry.
FYI, my noise-canceling headphones
proved ineffective last night.
(Penny:)-Yeah, sorry about that.
-As a native Texan, I must say...
...I've never heard the phrase "yeehaw"
used in quite that context.
(Penny:)Oh, God.
"Oh, God."
(Sheldon:)That I've heard on multiple occasions.
In what universe is that "lightly toasted"?
(Sheldon:)This has to be the worst day of my life.
(Sheldon:)Good morning, Leonard.
(Leonard:)How many times
have I asked you not to do that?
(Sheldon:)Counting this instance?
Three hundred seventeen.